The way that you talk about your own
identity is going to shape the actions
that you do on a subconscious level.
Like, I remember when I quit my job, I
was talking to a co-worker and I wanted
to tell them that I wanted to quit my
job and become an entrepreneur. But, it
was so uncomfortable for me to [music]
to say those words. Like, even though I
was just even messaging them. Like, I I
was like, "I think I'm going to do
entrepreneurship, lol." Not even
comfortable to say,
"I think I'm going to do this." And
there were some other conversations like
that where even though I knew this is
what I wanted to do, it was really
uncomfortable for me to say it and I
would say something like, "Yeah, I think
I'm going to try it out, you know, for a
few months and see." And, you know, if
it doesn't work out, then I'll apply for
a job or something. And it's really a
very bad way to approach something like
this. Because if I said those words, my
subconscious would would sort of believe
like, "Okay, so we're just doing this
for fun." And there's not really a
urgency.